Register of the Mark Sullivan Papers, 1883-1952
Hoover Institution Archives
Mark Sullivan Papers,
1883-1952
55007
Sullivan, Mark, 1874-1952
62 manuscript boxes, 10 scrapbooks, 3 envelopes. 35 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Correspondence, diaries, speeches and writings, memoranda, and printed matter, relating to journalism and to social, political, and economic developments in the United States.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1955.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Access Points
Journalism--United States.; Prohibition--United States.; United States--Politics and government.; United States--Economic conditions--1918-1945.; United States--Emigration and immigration.; United States--Politics and government--20th century.; United States--Social conditions--1918-1932.; United States--Social conditions--1933-1945.; Journalists.
Biographical Note
10 September 1874 Born, Avondale, Pennsylvania
1891 Newspaper reporter for the West Chester, Pennsylvania
1896 Entered Harvard University
1900 A.B., Harvard University
1903 LL.B., Harvard University
31 October 1907 Married Marie McMechan Buchanon
1912 Editor, Collier's Weekly
1919 Reporter for the New York Evening Post
1923-1952 Columnist for the New York Herald-Tribune
1924-1935 Author, Our Times - The United States, 6 volumes, 1900-1925
1927 Honorary Litt. D., Brown University
1928 Honorary Litt. D., Dartmouth University
1928 Overseer, Harvard University
1929 Bromley Lecturer, Yale University
1929 Board Visitors, U.S. Naval Academy
1933 Colonel, U.S.M.C. Reserve
1933 Honorary member, Phi Beta Kappa
1936 LL.D., Washington and Lee College
1936 LL.D., Bates College
1937 LL.D., St. John's College
1938 Author, The Education of an American (autobiography)
13 August 1952 Died, Avondale, Pennsylvania
Series Description
- DIARIES, 1922-1927. (Box Boxes 1-2)
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1883-1952. (Box Boxes 3-20)
  Arranged alphabetically by name of correspondent.
- SUBJECT FILE, 1888-1952. (Box Boxes 21-39)
  Printed matter, newspaper clippings, news releases, memoranda and other matter, arranged alphabetically by subject.
- WRITINGS, 1912-1951. (Box Boxes 40-57)
  Handwritten and typewritten unpublished writings and printed copies of published articles, arranged alphabetically by subseries as listed.
- SPEECHES AND BROADCASTS, 1939-1942. (Box Boxes 58-60)
  Handwritten and typewritten speeches and broadcasts arranged alphabetically by title or subject.
- MISCELLANY. (Box Boxes 61-62)
  Notebooks and oversized scrapbooks.
Container List
- DIARIES, 1922-1927
  - April 1-May 1922 (Box 1.)
  - June 18-December 13, 1922
  - January-February 1923
  - March 1-April 15, 1923
  - April 17-June 15, 1923
  - June 17-August 15, 1923
  - August 21-October 9, 1923
  - October 10-November 6, 1923
  - November 7, 1923-January 26, 1924 (Box 2.)
  - January 21, 1924-March 24, 1925
  - April 23, 1926-January 29, 1927
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1883-1952
  - Abbott, Ernest Hamlin, 1924 (Box 3.)
  - Acheson, Sam, 1932
  - Adams, A. M., 1935
  - Adams, C. E., 1920
  - Adams, John T., 1920
  - Adams, Samuel H., 1906
  - Agar, Herbert, 1943
  - Ailshire, Margaret Cross, 1932
  - Alber, Louis J., 1918-19
  - Albert, Allen D., 1943
  - Albro, H. W., 1928
  - Alexander, Edward A., 1944
  - Alexander, William C., 1935
  - Allen, Henry J., 1925-35
  - Allen, Henry T., 1923
  - Allen, Henry Ware, 1934
  - Allen, Robert McDowell, 1933-44
  - Amster, Hathan L., 1919
  - Anderson, C. E., 1945
  - Anderson, George Kerr, 1934
  - Anderson, Henry W., 1935
  - Anderson, William H., 1927-45
  - Andrews, C. S., 1905
  - Andrews, Matthew Page, 1910-45
  - Andrews, William N., 1920
  - Appenzallar, Edna Howell, n.d.
  - Apter, David, 1940
  - Argus Book Shop Inc., 1932-33
  - Arnn, Charles M., 1936
  - Arnold, Thurman, 1938
  - Aswell, E. C., 1928
  - Atherton, Gertrude, 1941
  - Atherton, Percy A., 1905
  - Atowell, John M., 1945
  - Atterbury, W. W., 1935
  - Atwood, M. V., 1929-33
  - Axe, E. W., 1935
  - Bacharach, Harry, 1935
  - Bacon, Verginia Murray, 1934
  - Baggerly, H. L., 1936
  - Bailey, Mrs. A. L., n.d.
  - Bailey, Josiah W., 1937-39
  - Bailey, L. M., 1937
  - Bailey, Temple, 1945
  - Baker, Newton, D., 1926-30
  - Ball, L. Heisler, 1920
  - Ballantine, Arthur A., 1921
  - Banner, Franklin, 1935
  - Barbee, David Tankin, 1929
  - Barbour, William R., 1934
  - Berkley, M. B., Jr., 1944
  - Barnes, A. J., 1934
  - Barnum, Jerome D., 1932
  - Barnum, W. L., 1920
  - Barr, Robert R., 1936
  - Barron, Clarence W., 1919
  - Baruch, Bernard, 1921-39
  - Basore, George W., 1935
  - Bass, Robert P., 1932
  - Battle, George G., 1938
  - Baver, O. F., 1926
  - Beacom, Madison W., 1903-09
  - Beale, Charles W., 1931-32
  - Beales, La Verne, 1924
  - Beane, A. S., 1932
  - Beane, Stephen, 1932
  - Beck, James M., 1935
  - Bede, Howard H., n.d.
  - Beeckman, Robert Livingston, 1920
  - Bell, Robert, 1922
  - Bellamy, Francis K., 1939
  - Belleres Falls Brewery, 1905
  - Benedict, D. Norris, 1934
  - Benner, N. W., 1922
  - Bennet, William S., 1910, 1933-36
  - Bennett, Edward, 1933
  - Bennett, Ira, 1935
  - Benson, Carville D., 1920
  - Benton, S. Miles, 1935-38
  - Berman, Nathan, 1943
  - Berman, Pemberton, 1935
  - Bernays, Edward L., 1932
  - Bertolet, James W., 1944
  - Best, Alfred M., 1944
  - Bethea, Andrew J., 1929
  - Beveridge, Albert J., 1906-27
  - Bevry, Charles E., 1936
  - Bickel, Karl A., 1938 (Box 4.)
  - Biddle, Nicholas, 1938
  - Bijor, Nathan J., 1934-35
  - Birdwell, Russell, 1943
  - Birmingham, W. C., 1929
  - Bishop, Joseph B., 1927
  - Blackmer, R. C., 1929
  - Blair, Mrs. Edward G., 1932
  - Blair, Emily Newell, 1928
  - Blair, Floyd Gilbert, 1932
  - Blair, Harry M., 1935
  - Blakeney, Albert A., 1920
  - Blanchard, Charles E., 1938
  - Blanchard, Edith G., 1941
  - Bliss, Mildred, 1945
  - Bliven, Bruce, 1922
  - Block, Paul, 1937
  - Bloom, Sol., 1929
  - Blythe, Samuel G., 1924
  - Boardman, Mabel T., 1937
  - Bodemann, Wilhelm, 1928
  - Boesel, Albert G., 1931-32
  - Bogert, John L., 1941-42
  - Bohleber, William, 1932
  - Boissevain, Robert, n.d.
  - Bok, Edward W., 1925
  - Bok, Mary Curtis, 1931
  - Bole, J. P., 1920
  - Bole, W. N., 1920
  - Bolling, Raynal C., 1916
  - Bond, Hulbert A., 1927
  - Bone, Scott, 1920
  - Boone, Joel T., 1935
  - Booth, Edmund W., 1920
  - Booth, George F., 1935
  - Borah, William F., 1920
  - Boren, Lyle H., 1942
  - Borland, John K, Jr., 1935
  - Bosler, William D., 1913
  - Bourne, George Lewis, 1935
  - Boorne, Jonathan, Jr., 1911
  - Bowie, Robert G., 1945
  - Bowie, Sydney J., 1918
  - Bowker, Mrs. William T., 1935
  - Bowles, Chester, 1944
  - Boyd, William P. 1932
  - Boyden, Albert A., 1905
  - Boyden, Charles E., 1929
  - Bramhall, John T., 1918
  - Brantley, W. G., 1933
  - Braunstein, Ethel, 1938
  - Brenckman, Fred, 1941
  - Breuster, Ralph O., 1939
  - Brain, Lee, 1932-33
  - Bridges, S. Russell, 1934-35
  - Briggs, Ernest, 1934
  - British Embassy, Washington, D. C., 1925
  - Britt, Albert, 1928
  - Britton, John J., 1945
  - Broderick, Joseph L., 1935
  - Brookhart, Smith W., 1942
  - Brooks, B. B., 1929
  - Brooks, Jacquline, 1938
  - Brown, Benjamin Henry Inness, 1933
  - Brown, C.Inness, 1921
  - Brown, Charles Paul, 1930
  - Brown, Edwin H., Jr., 1920
  - Brown, Ernest M., 1935
  - Brown, George Rothwell, 1935
  - Brown, George Stewart, 1932
  - Brown, H. Tatnall, 1933
  - Brown, James M., 1934
  - Brown, June Hardy, 1941
  - Brown, Lewis H., 1944
  - Brown, Paul, 1943
  - Brown, Phillip, n.d.
  - Brown, Steward, 1940
  - Brown, W. B., 1919
  - Brown, W. W., 1934
  - Brown, Walter, 1919
  - Brown, Wilson, 1939
  - Browne, Walter T., n.d.
  - Brubaker, Wilda, 1935
  - Bruce, Marion, n.d.
  - Bruere, Henry, 1933
  - Brush, Louis H., 1935
  - Bryan, John Stewart. 1921
  - Bryan, Julian Scott, 1928
  - Bryan, William Jennings, 1925
  - Buck, Gene, 1933
  - Buck, Solon J., 1945
  - Bull, Charles C., 1936
  - Bullard, F. Lauriston, 1932
  - Bullett, A. Scott, 1927
  - Bullett, William Marshall, 1932
  - Bungarz, H. W., 1932
  - Burch, Guy Irving, 1945
  - Burdick, Henry L., 1934
  - Burgess, William Henry, 1932
  - Burke, Edward R., 1938
  - Burke, James Francis, 1927
  - Burns, Charles, 1944
  - Burton, Theodore E., 1912
  - Busey, Harry F., 1936
  - Bush, A. G., 1945
  - Butcher, Fanny, 1928 (Box 5.)
  - Butler, Nicholas Murray, 1921-35
  - Butts, Louise M., 1945
  - Calder, William N., 1935
  - Caldwell, Edward J., 1934
  - Caldwell, R. J., 1919
  - Calkins, Ernest Elmo, 1930
  - Call, I. Slater, 1933
  - Callahan, Patrick Henry, 1926-33
  - Cameron, E. T., 1935
  - Cameron, Shelton T., 1934
  - Campbell, Arthur W., 1926
  - Campbell, Margaret T., 1936
  - Campbell, Phil, 1935
  - Campbell, Will A., 1920
  - Campion W. M., 1932
  - Canada, High Commissioner, 1900
  - Capital News, 1920
  - Capper, Arthur, n.d.
  - Carey, Joseph M., 1911
  - Carey, Robert D., 1932
  - Carmen, Bliss, 1920
  - Carothers, Neil, 1935
  - Carr, Beatrice E., 1945
  - Carrell, S. E., 1926
  - Carroll, H. K., 1928
  - Carroll, John H., 1930
  - Carry, Edward F., 1927
  - Case, Francis, 1942
  - Case, James H., Jr., n.d.
  - Case, Leland
  - Cassler, Howard R., 1937
  - Castle, William R., 1937
  - Chace, Benjamin B., 1935
  - Chadbourne, G. R., 1920-22
  - Chadbourne, William M., 1911-31
  - Chamberlin, Edwin, 1919
  - Chamberlin, Joseph E., 1926
  - Chamberlin, Rollo F., 1943
  - Chancellor, William E., 1935
  - Chandler, William D., 1920
  - Chandler, William E., 1910
  - Chapin, Roy D., 1929
  - Chapman, A. G., 1934
  - Chenery, William L., 1926-27
  - Child, A. C., 1938
  - Child, Richard W., 1921
  - Childs, Harry R., 1935
  - Chipley, Hunt, 1926
  - Chipman, H. L., 1920
  - Christian, George B., Jr., 1921
  - Clagett, Brice, 1932
  - Clapper, Raymond, 1934
  - Clark, Edward T., 1935
  - Clark, Eugene F., 1928
  - Clark, Grenville, 1932-43
  - Clark, John D., 1934
  - Clark, Lois Pinney, 1941
  - Clark, William, 1933
  - Clarke, John H., 1926
  - Clarkson, Grosvenor B., 1921-36
  - Clayburgh, Alma, 1926
  - Cleveland, L. K., 1932
  - Clemens, Cyril, 1928
  - Clements, Frank P., 1930
  - Clevenger, Logan, 1920
  - Clift, Fred W., 1920
  - Close, Joseph K., 1935
  - Cochran, Edwin R., 1931
  - Coe, Theodore Irving, 1940
  - Coe, William T., 1920
  - Coffin, Howard E., 1933
  - Coggeshad, Reginald, 1935
  - Cohalan, Daniel F., 1928
  - Cohen, Julius Henry, 1910
  - Coit, Arthur C., 1919
  - Colby, Bambridge, 1930-36
  - Colcord, Samuel, 1928
  - Coles, Charles A., 1933
  - Cole, Edward C., 1939
  - Coles, L. F., 1936
  - Colin, Ralph E., 1944
  - Collamore, Gilman, 1926
  - Colliers Weekly, 1908
  - Collmis, V. Lansurg, 1927
  - Comerford, William, 1929-30
  - Compton, Wilson, 1929
  - Connor, W. A., 1895
  - Cook, Harvey M., 1909
  - Cook, Willis, 1930
  - Coolidge, Calvin, 1931
  - Coolidge, Mrs. Calvin, 1935
  - Coolidge, L. A., 1920
  - Coombs, R. D., 1935
  - Cooney, E. H., 1920
  - Corbin, John, 1927
  - Cordeey, H. G., 1935
  - Cordingley, Nora E., 1937
  - Corey, Herbert, 1933
  - Corey, Maricin, 1935
  - Corradini, Robert E., 1927
  - Coryell, L. L., 1932-35
  - Costillo, L. B., 1930 (Box 6.)
  - Cotna, Philippe, 1935
  - Cotterell, C. A., 1918
  - Couch, H. C., 1927
  - Cowan, Austin N., 1933
  - Cowles, Johhn
  - Cowper, J. W., 1928
  - Cox, J. H., 1926
  - Cox, James M., 1921-35
  - Crane, Charles R., 1938
  - Crane, Charles W., 1932
  - Cranfill, J. B., 1927-28
  - Cranford, Chester S., 1935
  - Crawley, Kathleen, 1934
  - Creel, George, 1918-22
  - Criscuolo, Luigi, 1942
  - Crocker, Ruth Mercer, 1933
  - Crocker, William H., 1920
  - Croly, Harper, 1920
  - Cross, Wilbur, 1929
  - Crowell, John Franklin, n.d.
  - Culbertson, William S., 1921
  - Cullings, Evan R., 1945
  - Cummins, Albert B., 1970
  - Curran, Henry H., 1931
  - Curtis, Charles, 1935
  - Curtis, Cyrus H. K., 1931
  - Curtis, Emerson, 1928
  - Curtis, G. G., 1945
  - Cuthbertson, Stuart, 1937
  - Cutler, L. R., 1945
  - Cuvlier, Louis A., 1925-27
  - Dale, Ernest H., 1935
  - Dambly, B. Whitman, 1895
  - Daniels, Josephus, 1920-41
  - Danskin, Jas. H., 1920
  - Dantz, William T., 1912
  - Darling, Jay N., 1924-32
  - Darr, John W., 1934
  - Darrow, Whitney, 1933-34
  - Daugherty, Harry M., 1934-35
  - Daugherty, W. B., 1939
  - Davenport, A. H., 1919
  - Davenport, E., 1932
  - Davenport, Henry J., 1934
  - Davids, Mrs. Arthur E., 1941
  - Davies, Joseph E., 1934
  - Davis, A. F., 1939
  - Davis, Charles H., 1913-29
  - Davis, Dwight F., 1923
  - Davis, Edgar B., 1918
  - Davis, Forrest, 1940
  - Davis, James J., 1923-36
  - Davis, John, 1922
  - Davis, John W., 1924
  - Davis, Millard, 1934
  - Davis, William F., 1920
  - Davison, C. Beverly, 1942
  - Davison, F. Trubee, 1928
  - Davison, Herbert N., 1941
  - Dawes, Charles G., 1932
  - Dean, Arthur W., 1933
  - Decker, Frank N., 1928
  - Decker, H. C., 1935
  - De Cordova, M., 1904
  - Deffenbaugh, Greta S., 1938
  - DeFord, J. W., 1918
  - DeHaven, Henry N., 1943
  - DeLaplaine, Robert E., 1920
  - DeLatte, R. V., 1931
  - DeMary, Jackson, 1928
  - DeMeen, Charles A., 1932
  - Dennan, William, 1940
  - Dennis, Penn, 1928
  - Dennis, William C., 1909-10
  - DeRan, Hal C., 1933-35
  - Derby, Ethel Roosevelt, 1927-30
  - Desvernine, Raoul E., 1943
  - deTamble, Paul, 1942
  - Detling, Glenn, E., 1935
  - Dewey, Mrs. George, 1925
  - De Wolf, Maris C., 1934
  - Dexter, Edwin G., 1932
  - Dickey, Carl C., n.d.
  - Dickinson, John, 1934
  - Dickinson, William C., 1933
  - Dickson, Edward A., 1929
  - Dickson, Harris, 1926
  - Dickson, J. A., 1917
  - Dietrich, William, 1926
  - Dillon, John J., 1927
  - Disney, Wesley E., 1940
  - Dixon, Joseph M., 1920 (Box 7.)
  - Dobell, J. L., 1920
  - Dodd, William E., 1934
  - Donham, Wallace B., 1934
  - Donoghue, M. M., n.d.
  - Donovan, William, 1934-35
  - Dosch, E., 1937
  - Dougherty, Gerald A., 1945
  - Doughton, Isaac, 1936
  - Douglas, Cara M. David, 1934
  - Downey, Andrew A., 1918
  - Downey, Fairfax, 1932
  - Doyle, Arthur Conan, n.d.
  - Doyle, Denis Conan, 1940
  - Doyle, William F., 1944
  - Dowdy, Jackson G., 1932
  - Draper, Charles H., 1920
  - Drinkwater, Arthur, 1925
  - Drufner, V. H., 1935-36
  - Drury, Samuel A., 1927
  - Dudley, H. C., 1931
  - Dunham, Alice W., 1926
  - Dunn, C., 1909
  - Dunn, W. F., 1920
  - Du Pont, L., 1936
  - Durland, Frank, 1941
  - Dussere, Louis, 1933
  - DuVal, J. Herbert, 1932
  - Early, Stephen T., 1933-49
  - Eaton, Cyrus A., 1941
  - Ecker, Frederick H., 1933
  - Edge, Walter E., 1929
  - Edmonds, Richard H., 1925-28
  - Edmonson, Robert Edward, 1934
  - Edwards, Frank W., 1932
  - Ehrlich, Howard, 1938
  - Eiselein, A. H., 1920
  - Eilers, Karl, 1935
  - Eliah, Karl, 1945
  - Eliot, George Fielding, 1946
  - Elliot, Howard, 1925
  - Elliot, J. Jay, 1934-35
  - Emmett, Elizabeth, 1933
  - Enoch, William, 1935
  - Erickman, G., 1935
  - Ernst, Richard P., 1920
  - Esterbrook, Fred W., 1920
  - Esty, J. Carleton, 1935
  - Evans, Dorothy Hopkins, 1945
  - Evans, P. E., 1920
  - Evans, Helen H., 1937
  - Evans, L. P., 1920
  - Evans, Rudolph M., 1941
  - Everitt, C. R., 1934
  - Ezekiel, Mordecai, 1933
  - Fackler, John D., 1911
  - Fadiman, Clifton, 1945
  - Fancher, Edith, 1933-34
  - Fankhaiser, Charles Kingsley, 1936
  - Farish, George E., 1934
  - Farley, Belmont, 1943
  - Fast, Carl, n.d.
  - Fay, Charles N., 1936
  - Feli´v -H. Luis E., 1929
  - Fell, A. W., 1934-35
  - Fell, Emily J., 1936
  - Ferber, Edna, 1934
  - Field, Carter, 1935
  - Filene, Edward A., 1911
  - Finich, Edward R., 1910
  - Finney, Edward C., 1935
  - Finty, Tom Jr., 1928
  - Fish, Hamilton, 1937
  - Fisher, S. M., 1945
  - Fitch, C. L., 1933
  - Fitzsimmons, Florencé, 1933
  - Fluck, John J., n.d.
  - Flanagan, E. L., 1928
  - Flanagan, Roy, 1932
  - Fletcher, Henry P., 1931, 1934
  - Flynn, John T., 1937
  - Foley, James W., 1905
  - Folger, B. W., 1934
  - Folk, Joseph W., 1911-23
  - Folwell, Charles H., 1920
  - Fonthein, Nadenia, 1938
  - Forbes, Charles R., 1934
  - Ford, John Anson, 1927
  - Fordham, Herbert, 1933
  - Formann, Paris R., 1941
  - Forster, Henry A., 1919
  - Forsythe, Holmes, 1936
  - Foster, Edwin L., 1920
  - Foster, G. M., 1936
  - Foulker, Thomas L., 1932
  - Fox, Adaline, n.d.
  - Fox, Alan, 1935
  - Fox, Henry H., 1933
  - Fox, M. L., 1928
  - France, Joseph I., 1935
  - France, R. M., 1932
  - Freeman, George F., 1936
  - Frelinghuysen, J. S., 1923-35
  - French, John A., 1935
  - Freund, Sanford H. E., 1945
  - Frick, Helen C., 1935
  - Frost, G. B., 1936
  - Frost, Robert, 1926
  - Fuller, J. E., 1937
  - Furber, P. N., 1945
  - Fyfe, Hamilton, 1917
  - Gair, Ernest J., 1936 (Box 8.)
  - Galbraith, M. H., 1935
  - Gall, John C., 1942
  - Gallagher, Thomas W., 1920
  - Gammack, Thomas H., 1933
  - Gannett, Frank E., 1927-51
  - Gannett, Guy P., 1920-22
  - Garber, Al C., 1935
  - Garfield, James R., 1932
  - Garrett, Robert, 1938
  - Gaylord, Raymond, 1935
  - Geoffrey, Martin, 1930-33
  - Getts, Clark H., 1935
  - Gilbert, E. A., 1926
  - Gilchrist, Raleigh, 1932
  - Gillespie, H. C., 1930
  - Gillett, Frederick H., 1935
  - Gillett, J. N., Jr., 1935
  - Gitterman, A. N., 1934
  - Glass, Carter, 1923
  - Glasscock, W. R., 1919
  - Glenn, John J., 1932
  - Goddin, Burt M., 1932-33
  - Godwin, Earl, 1945
  - Gold, Theodore A., 1919
  - Golding, E., 1920
  - Goldthorp, Mrs. E. A., 1933
  - Gompers, Samuel, 1923
  - Gonzales, William E., 1922
  - Goodale, Grace Harriet, 1941
  - Goodwin, J. Pryse, 1945
  - Gordon, Max, 1936-38
  - Gordon, Sloane, 1921
  - Goree, C. P., 1920
  - Graham, John A., 1934
  - Graham, Whidden, 1929
  - Gray, Agnes, 1937
  - Gray, Jessie, 1945
  - Green, Charles A., 1935
  - Green, F. H., 1920
  - Green, Henry, 1932
  - Green, Horace, 1932
  - Greenbie, Sydney, 1934
  - Greene, Charles T., 1932
  - Greene, Gertrude Marie, 1933
  - Greene, Frank L., 1923-27
  - Greene, Ruth L., n.d.
  - Greene, Thomas H., 1934
  - Gregory, Ruth H., 1945
  - Grey, Monica H., 1934-35
  - Griffin, W. H., Jr., 1926-27
  - Griffith, John L., 1934
  - Griffith, William, 1935
  - Grill, Louis F., 1920
  - Griscern, Acton, 1945
  - Griswold, Glenn, 1936
  - Groner, Lawrence D., 1932
  - Grosvenor, Edwin A., 1933
  - Grover, Edwin O., 1936
  - Guilherme, Olympio, 1933
  - Gunter, H. B., 1909
  - Gutheim, Frederick A., 1928
  - Guzy, Chas., 1935
  - Haga, Oliver O., 1934
  - Hagedorn, Hermann, 1923-45
  - Hahn, George P., 1932
  - Haines, Laura, n.d.
  - Hale, Frederick, 1935
  - Halifax, Edward, F.L.W., 1943
  - Hall, Blakely, 1913
  - Hall, Dwight, 1920
  - Halliday, Clark W., 1934
  - Hamlin, Chauncey J., 1940
  - Hamlin, Elbert B., 1933
  - Hamilton, Clayton, 1929
  - Hammesfahr, A.C.G., 1917-18
  - Hammond, John Harp, 1910-34
  - Hampton, Banjamin B., 1914
  - Han, Frank J., 1922
  - Hand, G. C., 1906-35
  - Hanrahan, James C., 1932
  - Hanson, Marybelle H., 1936
  - Hapgood, Norman, 1906-08
  - Hardee, Theodore, 1919
  - Harden, Francis L., 1930
  - Harding, Warren G., 1921-22
  - Hardy, Guy V., 1920
  - Hardy, Katherine DeF., n.d.
  - Hardy, W. F., 1920
  - Harper, F. A., 1943
  - Harreld, John W., 1935
  - Harriman, Joseph W., 1929
  - Harris, H. H., 1942
  - Harris, John F., 1933
  - Harrison, Ernest R., 1931
  - Harry, W. D., 1933
  - Hart, Irving W., 1932 (Box 9.)
  - Hart, Malcolm L., 1918
  - Hart, Thomas C., 1942
  - Hartt, Rollin L., 1906
  - Harvard, John, 1933
  - Harvey, E. L., 1918
  - Harvey, George, 1921
  - Harvey, William Hope, 1924-26
  - Harvier, Ernest, 1922
  - Haskell, Henry J., 1923
  - Hastings, Daniel O., 1942
  - Havens, Munson, 1934
  - Haverstick and Company, 1922
  - Hawkes, Albert W., 1942
  - Hayden, Charles, 1935
  - Hayden, Donald A., 1932
  - Hays, Will, 1921-35
  - Hayward, William, 1921-32
  - Heald, K. C., 1935
  - Heathcote, Charles W., 1932
  - Hedin, Naboth, 1934
  - Hefferman, John V., 1936
  - Henderson, H. B., 1937
  - Heney, Francis J., 1932
  - Henry, Phillip W., 1926
  - Herring, Clyde L., 1923
  - Herriott, Frank I., 1935
  - Herron, L. Z., n.d.
  - Hershey, Lloyd E., 1941
  - Hert, A. T., 1920
  - Herzog, Paul M., 1945
  - Hewes, Clarence B., 1939
  - Heyd, Charles G., 1936
  - Hickey, J. G., 1932
  - Hicks, Clarence J., 1934
  - Higbie, Robert W., 1932
  - Higgins, John W., 1934
  - Hill, John Phillip, 1920
  - Hilles, Charles D., 1935
  - Hilton, J. Ralph, 1920
  - Hinshaw, Daird, 1938
  - Hitchcock, Frank, 1935
  - Hitchcock, Senator Gilbert, 1921
  - Hoagland, C. P., 1920
  - Hoban, C. F., 1935
  - Hobbs, Conrad, 1920
  - Hobbs, Sam, 1940
  - Hochschild, Harold K., 1947
  - Hodges, Leigh Mitchell, n.d.
  - Hodges, Louis O., 1933
  - Hodges, William V., 1926
  - Hogan, Barney, 1932
  - Hogan, Frank J., 1920-35
  - Holbrook, Royal H., 1931
  - Holland, Rush L., 1935
  - Holloway, C. C., 1920
  - Holman, Alfred, 1918-26
  - Holmes, W. E., 1931
  - Hood, Horace, 1920-23
  - Hooker, Elon H., 1923
  - Hoover, Richard, 1929
  - Hoover, Herbert C., 1920-38
  - Hoover, Herbert C., 1939-1952 (Box 10.)
  - Hoover, Lewis W., 1941
  - Hope, Walter E., 1935
  - Hopper, Elmer F., 1935
  - Hopper W. W., 1937
  - Hopkins, Arthur H., 1935
  - Hopkins, Ernest M., 1928
  - Hopkins, S. W., 1919
  - Hornaday, James P., 1935
  - Hotchkin, Alice M., 1934
  - House, R. D., 1943
  - Houston, D. F., 1933
  - Houston, J. P., 1932
  - Hovenden, Martha M., 1935
  - Howard, Arthur L., 1926
  - Howard, Clinton N., 1932
  - Howard, William G., 1932
  - Howe, M. A. DeWolfe, 1933
  - Howe, Will D., n.d.
  - Howell, Clark, 1920
  - Howell, R. B., 1923
  - Howell, Thomas J., 1919
  - Howland, E. A., 1935
  - Hoyt, William T., 1932
  - Hubbard, S. T., 1931
  - Hubbell, Mark H., 1934
  - Hubbert, R. L., 1938
  - Huber, Martha B., 1932
  - Hudson, Henry, 1926
  - Hudson, J. E., 1935
  - Hughes, A. D., 1931
  - Hughes, Charles Evans, 1921
  - Hull, Harry, 1909
  - Humphrey, Fred B., n.d.
  - Hungerford, Arthur E., 1921
  - Hunt, Edgar W., 1936
  - Hunt, Edward Eyre, 1929
  - Hunt, Herbert S., 1926
  - Hunter, Louis C., 1937
  - Huntington, Edward V., 1933
  - Hurely, Edward N., 1929
  - Hurley, Patrick J., 1932
  - Hutchinson, John, 1934
  - Hutchinson, John W., 1932
  - Hutchinson, Ralph C., 1935
  - Huttinger, E. Paul, 1939
  - Hyde, Arthur M., 1934
  - Ihnken, Charles G., 1945
  - Ingham, Harvey, 1920-29
  - Inglis, William O., 1928-29
  - Ions, Clarenden, 1941
  - Ives, Frederick, Manley, 1914-39
  - Jackson, H. Nelson, 1944
  - Jackson, Robert, 1932-42
  - Jachncke, Ernest Lee, 1929-33
  - Jameson, John F., 1935
  - Jarrell, J. G., 1917
  - Javits, Benjamin A., 1941
  - Jaynes, Allan B., 1920
  - Jeffery's, Upton S., 1920
  - Jelke, Ferdinand Jr., 1936
  - Jenkins, James E., 1927-35
  - Jenkins, Jas. D., 1918
  - Jenner, H. H., 1930
  - Jennings, Annie B., 1935-36
  - Johnson, Arthur, 1932
  - Johnson, Arthur, 1935
  - Johnson, George E., 1932
  - Johnson, Harold B., 1930-37
  - Johnson, Herbert, 1935
  - Johnson, Hiram, 1935
  - Johnson, Hugh, 1933
  - Johnson, Laurence, B., 1934
  - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1943
  - Johnson, Mark L., 1935
  - Johnson, William H., 1936